

jmcb1995@hotmail.com.ar

1138042688

(S) Congreso, CABA, Argentina

in Profile Linkedin

Portfolio Github

## **EDUCATION**

<u>Instituto Almirante</u>
 <u>Guillermo Brown</u>

Primary school and high school 2001 - 2011

 Instituto Nueva Escuela del Sur

Bachelor of Social Sciences
Completed in 2014

# **SKILLS**

- SQL (PL/SQL MsSQL)
- Power BI
- Excel
- AWS (Cloudwatch)
- ETL
- JIRA
- Service Now

# **LANGUAGES**

English

Oral level: Professional Written level: Professional

Spanish

Native

# Juan Manuel Chuit Berzoni Application Support

# **PROFILE**

I am an Application Support Analyst with experience in the IT industry. I have a solid understanding of the software development life cycle. I am also an excellent communicator and have a proven track record of resolving customer issues in a timely and efficient manner.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### **Global Processing | Application Support Analyst**

2022 - Present

- •Analysis and monitoring of productive incidents in acquisition.
- •Perform development tests on incident resolution.

### <u>Stefanini Group | Help Desk</u> 2021 – 2022

- · Resolution of incidents with first level tools
- Resolution with internal and external users.

#### <u>YEL Solutions | Access Management</u> 2020 - 2021

- Add, remove, and modify users in Active Directory.
- Unlocks and rehabilitation of accounts.

# **CERTIFICATES**

Drive with courses and certificates